https://fibroids.com/patient-privacy-policy/

Patient Privacy Policy - Treatment for Uterine Fibroids
HomeSuccess StoriesEmbolizationUterine Fibroid EmbolizationAdvantagesSee it WorkWhat to ExpectFor Patients Outside of CaliforniaFrequently Asked QuestionsAsk a QuestionFibroid SymptomsFibroid InfoHeavy BleedingPainful SexPelvic PainEnlarged UterusFibroids and Weight GainTreatmentsNonsurgicalHysterectomyMyomectomyInformationBest Treatments For FibroidsWhat are Uterine Fibroids?Protect Your FertilityGeneral GynecologyFibroids and Back PainVideosEventsContact UsAbout UsThe FTC DifferenceFibroid ExpertsChristina Economides, M.D.Tina Hardley, M.D.Bruce McLucas, M.D., FTC FounderRamin Mirhashemi, M.D.Richard Reed, M.D.Babak Yaghmai, M.D.Katrine Zhiroff, M.D.Press RoomFibroid MorcellationBlogHealth InformationIn the NewsFertilityBreaking NewsMedical NewsVideo & Radio InterviewsVideo & Radio InterviewsPatient QuestionsNewslettersSchedule an AppointmentFree Consultation (866) 479-1523Contact UsAbout UsBlogFree Consultation HomeFibroid InfoFibroid SizesFertility & FibroidsMenopause & FibroidsGeneral GynecologyFibroid SymptomsHeavy BleedingPainful SexPelvic PainEnlarged UterusFibroids and Weight GainFibroids and InfertilityTreatmentsNon-Surgical EmbolizationHysterectomyMyomectomyEmbolizationWhat to Expect From Fibroid EmbolizationAdvantages of EmbolizationFrequently Asked QuestionsSee it WorkResourcesEventsFor Patients Outside of CAVideosClinical EvidenceSuccess StoriesEn EspañolHome » Patient Privacy PolicyShare the post "Patient Privacy Policy"FacebookTwitterGoogle+PinterestE-mailPatient Privacy PolicyConfidentiality, first and foremost.Any interaction you have with FTC, whether it’s a simple email or an office visit, will never be shared without your express consent. As a professional medical facility, we strictly adhere to the practices outlined in the Patient Privacy Document (linked below). The stories, interviews and emails that appear on this site are from patients who felt strongly and positively enough about their experience with embolization to assist FTC in informing and educating other women.Use of email addressesEmail addresses which are collected on this site are used solely for the purpose of communicating with an individual about Fibroid Treatment Collective business. Unless otherwise indicated, by submitting your email address to us on this site, you give us permission to contact you regarding the subject of your communication. We do not sell addresses or share them with any other entity.You may choose to submit your email address to us in order to receive communications about the Fibroid Treatment Collective, including announcements about this Website and other news regarding the Fibroid Treatment Collective. Any page requesting email addresses for this purpose will clearly state the intended use and will provide instructions for how to unsubscribe.Security of emailEmails sent through the the Fibroid Treatment Collective Website via the “Ask a Question” or “Free Consultation” page are not secure. Please be advised that we cannot guarantee the security of personal health information that you send to us via email through this site. However, by sending us an email, you give the Fibroid Treatment Collective permission to respond to you via email about that subject.Privacy of user information collected on this WebsiteThe Fibroid Treatment Collective is committed to protecting the privacy of all users of this Website. We do not sell or release information obtained or collected through this Website, including email addresses, to anyone.The Fibroid Treatment Collective collects anonymous navigation information to evaluate the usefulness of our Website. We also collect contact information at the request of prospective members to inform them about the plan.We may use aggregate information collected about users for the purpose of reporting on or improving the Website. This information cannot be used to personally identify an individual, but does help us create a better Website. The type of information we collect includes:Date and time of visitIP address (a unique number assigned to each server that accesses the Internet)Browser type (such as Internet Explorer or Netscape Navigator)Platform type (such as Windows or Macintosh)Pages visited on this WebsiteReferring sites (including search engines used)Geographic locationInternet service provider (such as AOL)The Fibroid Treatment Collective is fully compliant with the federal government regulations regarding the privacy of personal health information as outlined in the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (HIPAA).Any personal health information sent to The Fibroid Treatment Collective through this Website will be kept strictly confidential.For additional details, you can download a PDF version of our Patient Privacy Policy Michelle ended fibroids. And her fear of early menopause.
It (fibroids) affected my mood, my energy, I just couldn’t seem to have enough energy to do some of the things that I wanted to do with my children and my spouse Read moreTop Articles Fighting Fibroids Without Surgery The Truth About PVA Particles Fibroids Inside and Outside of the Uterus Are Physical Health and Emotional Health Related? Depression and FibroidsNext Event
In the News
The Doctor and
the DJ talk fibroids
Tuesday, October 18, 2016
Dr. McLucas at KJLH Health Fair
Monday, June 27, 2016
Fibroid Morcellation: A Cautionary Tale
Tuesday, March 24, 2015Facing a hysterectomy or other surgery? Find out if embolization is right for you!Call (866) 479-1523 or Click Here
FibroidsNext Event
Success StoriesFibroid SymptomsTreatmentsEmbolization (UFE)Patient Privacy PolicyPress RoomContact UsSitemapResources
The Fibroid Treatment Collective
9201 Sunset Blvd, #401 West Hollywood, CA 90069 United States
© 2020 The Fibroid Treatment Collective. All Rights Reserved. FTC offers free phone consultations to any patient. Free in-office consultations are available for new patients only. *Disclaimer: The ideas, procedures, and suggestions contained on this website are not intended as a substitute for consulting with your physician. All matters regarding your health require medical supervision. Uterine Fibroid Embolization has been known to provide relief from their symptoms and significant fibroid shrinkage. Results may vary for individuals.
| Optimized and Maintained by
Am I a candidate for non-surgical treatment? Click herex
